<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kozy Macro - Knight Online Makro - Rise Online Makro</title>
    <link>https://kozymacro.com/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kozy Macro - Knight Online Makro - Rise Online Makro</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://kozymacro.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Knight Online Assassin Macro Guide - Perfect Combo Experience with Kozy Macro</title>
      <link>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/assassin-combo-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/assassin-combo-guide/</guid>
      <description>For players using Assassin (Rogue) characters in Knight Online, one of the most critical elements is combos performed with precise timing. Performing a perfect assassin combo manually is extremely difficult and exhausting. This is where Kozy Macro&amp;rsquo;s Assassin Combo feature comes into play.&#xA;What is Assassin Macro? Assassin macro is an intelligent system specially developed for rogue characters in Knight Online and Rise Online, which tracks skill cooldown times and can perform first-class assassin combos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knight Online Kurian Macro Guide - Two Powerful Combos with Kozy Macro</title>
      <link>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/kurian-macro-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/kurian-macro-guide/</guid>
      <description>In Knight Online, the Kurian character stands out with both poisonous attacks and powerful physical combos as a unique class. Using the right combo is vital to unleash Kurian&amp;rsquo;s true potential. Kozy Macro&amp;rsquo;s Kurian feature offers you two different combo options: Smash (Poison) Combo and 75-63-60 Attack Combo.&#xA;What is Kurian Macro? Knight Online Kurian macro is an advanced combo system that supports this character&amp;rsquo;s two different playstyles. You can determine which combo to use in which situation and achieve maximum efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knight Online Minor Macro Guide - Instant Healing with Kozy Macro</title>
      <link>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/minor-macro-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/minor-macro-guide/</guid>
      <description>In Knight Online, the Minor skill is a life-saving ability that allows you to instantly heal yourself in critical situations. Especially during PK and in challenging farming areas, using minor at maximum speed when your HP drops can keep you alive. Kozy Macro&amp;rsquo;s Minor feature is designed to help you manage these critical moments.&#xA;What is Minor Macro? Minor macro is a system that allows you to use the minor skill available to all characters in Knight Online at maximum speed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knight Online Restore/Debuff Removal Macro Guide - Instant Debuff Clearing with Kozy Macro</title>
      <link>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/restore-debuff-removal-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/restore-debuff-removal-guide/</guid>
      <description>In Knight Online, debuff skills during PK can be players&amp;rsquo; biggest nightmare. Torment, parasite, sword or other negative effects can leave you defenseless in critical moments. With Kozy Macro&amp;rsquo;s Restore/Debuff Removal feature, you can clear these debuffs instantly with one key and keep control of the game in your hands.&#xA;What is Restore/Debuff Removal Macro? This feature is an intelligent system that allows you to quickly remove unwanted skills cast on you in Knight Online with a single key.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customized Macro</title>
      <link>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/customized-macro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/customized-macro/</guid>
      <description>Kozy allows you to define your own customized macros. You can record key presses/mouse clicks and color conditions. Easy to use user interface let you define everything with few clicks. The custom macros work on every game!&#xA;Basics There are two different custom macro button under the farm section and pk section.&#xA;Farm macros always start when the farm macro triggered. (Usually F11.)&#xA;PK macros can be controlled by using the key you have assigned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Kozy Makro?</title>
      <link>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/what-is-kozy-makro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/what-is-kozy-makro/</guid>
      <description>A macro can move your mouse automatically and can use your keyboard&amp;rsquo;s keys seamlessly.&#xA;There is an animation and cooldown time for the skills you can use on the Knight Online. Giving the best possible damage can be hard for you but not for macro.&#xA;Game hacks inject some malicius code to the games or touch the game files. This is not allowed. But macro softwares don&amp;rsquo;t interfere like that. Works like a mouse/keyboard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardware Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://kozymacro.com/en/hardware/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kozymacro.com/en/hardware/privacy/</guid>
      <description>KOZY HARDWARE PRIVACY POLICY&#xA;Last Updated: September 2025&#xA;This Hardware Privacy Policy describes how Kozymacro collects, uses, and protects information related to the Kozy Hardware device and its integration with our software services.&#xA;SECTION I: INFORMATION WE COLLECT&#xA;1.1. Hardware Device Information&#xA;When you use Kozy Hardware, we may collect:&#xA;Device serial number and firmware version Hardware connectivity status and performance metrics Device usage patterns and feature utilization Error logs and diagnostic information from the device 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardware Terms &amp; Conditions</title>
      <link>https://kozymacro.com/en/hardware/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kozymacro.com/en/hardware/terms/</guid>
      <description>KOZY HARDWARE TERMS &amp;amp; CONDITIONS&#xA;Last Updated: September 2025&#xA;The Kozy Hardware device and related services are provided by Kozymacro, a Turkey company with a principal place of business located at İstanbul.&#xA;SECTION I: DEFINITIONS&#xA;1.1. Definitions.&#xA;References to &amp;ldquo;Hardware&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Kozy Hardware&amp;rdquo; mean the physical USB device and related firmware provided by Kozymacro for hardware-level macro functionality.&#xA;References to &amp;ldquo;Device&amp;rdquo; mean the Kozy Hardware USB device, including all physical components, firmware, and accompanying cables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardware Warranty Certificate</title>
      <link>https://kozymacro.com/en/hardware/warranty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kozymacro.com/en/hardware/warranty/</guid>
      <description>KOZY HARDWARE WARRANTY CERTIFICATE&#xA;Last Updated: September 2025&#xA;This warranty certificate details the official warranty coverage and conditions provided for your Kozy Hardware device.&#xA;WARRANTY COVERAGE&#xA;Warranty Period: 24 months (From delivery date)&#xA;Covered Conditions:&#xA;Manufacturing defects and material flaws Functionality issues under normal use Firmware-related malfunctions Connectivity problems (excluding USB port wear) Software integration issues CONDITIONS NOT COVERED BY WARRANTY&#xA;Physical damage (drops, impacts, pressure) Water damage or moisture exposure Extreme temperature or cold environment damage Electrical overload damage Device modification or opening Unauthorized repair attempts Normal wear and tear Misuse or abuse Software license expiration (does not affect hardware functionality) WARRANTY TERMS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://kozymacro.com/en/terms/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kozymacro.com/en/terms/privacy/</guid>
      <description>We at Kozymacro are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our data processing practices and your options regarding the ways in which your personal data is used and is provided by Kozymacro, a Turkey company. If you have requests concerning your personal information or any questions please contact us kozymacro@gmail.com.&#xA;If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should immediately discontinue use of the Web site and the Services offered by us.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
