<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pedal on Kozy Macro - Knight Online Makro - Rise Online Makro</title>
    <link>https://kozymacro.com/en/tags/pedal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pedal on Kozy Macro - Knight Online Makro - Rise Online Makro</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://kozymacro.com/en/tags/pedal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Knight Online Minor Macro Guide - Instant Healing with Kozy Macro</title>
      <link>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/minor-macro-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/minor-macro-guide/</guid>
      <description>In Knight Online, the Minor skill is a life-saving ability that allows you to instantly heal yourself in critical situations. Especially during PK and in challenging farming areas, using minor at maximum speed when your HP drops can keep you alive. Kozy Macro&amp;rsquo;s Minor feature is designed to help you manage these critical moments.&#xA;What is Minor Macro? Minor macro is a system that allows you to use the minor skill available to all characters in Knight Online at maximum speed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knight Online Restore/Debuff Removal Macro Guide - Instant Debuff Clearing with Kozy Macro</title>
      <link>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/restore-debuff-removal-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kozymacro.com/en/blog/restore-debuff-removal-guide/</guid>
      <description>In Knight Online, debuff skills during PK can be players&amp;rsquo; biggest nightmare. Torment, parasite, sword or other negative effects can leave you defenseless in critical moments. With Kozy Macro&amp;rsquo;s Restore/Debuff Removal feature, you can clear these debuffs instantly with one key and keep control of the game in your hands.&#xA;What is Restore/Debuff Removal Macro? This feature is an intelligent system that allows you to quickly remove unwanted skills cast on you in Knight Online with a single key.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
